Josh Budrow

Software Engineer 7820 Baymeadows Rd E Jacksonville, FL 32256 JBudrowD3@gmail.com (404) 518-6204 Jbudrow.github.io

"There is no greater education than one that is self-driven."
-Neil DeGrasse Tyson

Skills



CSS

HTML

RDBMS (PostgreSQL, MySQL)

Ruby on Rails

Tools

Heroku, Sinatra, RSpec, Cucumber, TravisCI, Fabrication, Devise, Kaminari, Haml, DelayedJob, Amazon Web Service, Bootstrap, Logstash, Git, Github, Datadog, Zsh

Projects

Cabin Fever

3 Week Duration

2 Back-End, 2 Front-End Developers

Cabin Fever is an app that seeks to make finding that perfect cabin easier. We provide a place where cabin owners, regardless of which management company they use, can list their cabin for rent and have their guests share their experiences.

Votr

3 Day Duration

2 Back-End, 2 Front-End Developers

Users can view live political polling feed of votes going on locally, or nationally.

Education

Gordon State College

Barnesville, Ga Fall 2011 Humanities Major

Certifications | HIPPA Compliant

Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act BioIQ Aug 2016 - Aug 2018

Back End Engineer

Certificate of Completion The Iron Yard May 2016

Experience

Ruby on Rails Support Engineer // BioIQ

Atlanta, Ga Aug 2016 - Current

Utilize Ruby on Rails among other libraries such as haml, cucumber, RSpec; provide internal support for BioIQ's products and services. Respond to incoming requests for support and drive informed and timely solutions. Drive the design of solutions implemented for clients and work with other Engineers in the delivery of new technical implementations.

Software Engineer // Hack-A-Thon

Atlanta, Ga Apr 2016

Weekend event hosted by The Iron Yard, which a large number of people meet to engage in collaborative computer programming.

Software Engineer // The Iron Yard

Atlanta, Ga Feb 2016 - May 2016

Twelve-week intensive immersion coding program. Back End Curriculum including but not limited to Ruby on Rails, data analytics, object oriented principles, testdriven development, agile development.

Maintenance Mechanic // Pitt Plastics Inc.

Morrow, Ga Nov 2014 - Sept 2015

Responsible for setting up/repairing thermoformers, trimpresses, and extruders. Install, repair, maintain all mechanical hydraulic, pneumatic equipment in the facility. Other duties include rebuilding spare parts, replacing machine blades, and working with other maintenance personnel.